(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T13:57:39.942081",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
聞こえますか？ 聞こえますか？
Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
Hello? Are we live?
イエーイ！ Let's go!
Yeah! Let's go!
ガイコツちゃん！ Everybody, hi!
Gaikotsu-chan! Everybody, hi!
It's my birthday! It's my birthday!
We're live, yatta! Okay, I'm seeing the chat now.
We're live, yay! Okay, I'm seeing the chat now.
We're live! Yeah, yeah, sorry for the little delay.
We're live! Yeah, sorry for the little delay.
Everybody, Gaikotsu-chan is here to celebrate. Unlucky deadbeat!
ガイコツちゃん かわいい かわいい ガイコツちゃん だいすき！イエーイ！
Gaikotsu-chan so cute, so cute, I love Gaikotsu-chan! Yeah!
寂しくないよ 寂しくないよ ガイコツちゃんいるから！
I'm not lonely, I'm not lonely because Gaikotsu-chan is here!
イエーイ！ 超かわいいね！
Yeah! So cute!
Because my skeleton friend is here, I don't feel alone,
but I also don't feel alone because you guys are here with me.
Welcome, welcome to my karaoke room. Check it out, it's made for me.
Welcome, welcome to my karaoke room.
Check it out, it's made for me.
It's all made for me.
Busted down, busted down, busted down, busted down... Sorry! I'm really happy.
Busted down, busted down, busted down...
Sorry! I'm really happy.
I'm happy because guess what everyone, I'm officially no years old. 相変わらず、ね？
I'm happy because guess what everyone, I'm officially zero years old. Still the same, right?
Yes, that's right. Happy birthday everyone. I'm reading the comments too. Cute, cute! Thank you so much.
Yes, that's right. Happy birthday everyone.
I'm reading the comments too. Cute, cute! Thank you so much.
You guys like the balloons? Balloons!
ふうせんもあるね。そう、かわいいね、スカルみたいなやつもあるからほら見て。最高ね。
There are balloons too. Yeah, so cute,
there's even skull-like ones, look at that. Awesome.
かわよ！ Happy birthday Mori, thank you so much!
So cute! Happy birthday Mori, thank you so much!
You guys want to sing some songs? We're in a karaoke booth, right? So let's sing some songs!
You guys want to sing some songs?
We're in a karaoke booth, right? So let's sing some songs!
I prepared a lot of songs today. There are quite a few new ones too. So get excited, minna,
I prepared a lot of songs today.
There are quite a few new ones too. So get excited everyone,
わくわくしてる？ わくわくしてる？
are you excited? Are you excited?
ガイコツちゃんわくわくしてるよね！
Gaikotsu-chan is excited too, right?
Yeah, let's go! Mr. Bones, Mr. Bones!
Mr. Bones, Mr. Bones...
Na, it's okay. You guys'لل see. 骸骨ちゃん is a really good dancer.
Nah, it's okay. You guys'll see. Gaikotsu-chan's a really good dancer.
Get ready. ワクワク？ワクワクね？
Get ready. Excited? Excited, right?
ねえ、骸骨ちゃん？ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Right, Gaikotsu-chan? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
はあ、すごい。
Hah, amazing.
あ、でも、なんか元気すぎるからちょっとすぐにヘッドヘッドになっちゃうからちょっと落ち着きます。
Ah, but I'm getting way too energetic and about to get dizzy, so I'm gonna calm down a bit.
はあ。はい。じゃあ、曲歌いましょう。Let's sing songs. You guys ready? We should sing. Okay, let's go!
Hah. Yeah. Alright, let's sing songs. Let's sing. You guys ready? We should sing. Okay, let's go!
First song.
皆さん、モリカリオペの 彼氏の誕生日
Everyone, it's Mori Calliope's... boyfriend's birthday!
ようこそ！Waku-waku! Happy birthday everyone!
Welcome! So exciting! Happy birthday everyone!
The first song is...
GUNDAM!
Hey, hey! Come on! 懐かしいね！
Hey, hey! Come on! This brings back memories!
擦れ違い 急ぐ度に ぶつけ合い散切れ合う
Every time we hurry past each other, we hit and tear ourselves
互いの羽根の 痛み感じている
we feel the pain of each other's wings.
淋しさに汚れた 腕で抱いた それ以外の何かをも知らないから
Embraced in unclean arms of loneliness, because I know nothing else.
繋がる瞬間 目覚める永遠 待ち焦がれる
The moment we connect, eternity awakens, I long for it.
速過ぎる時の 瞬きに晒されて 一人では届かない 願いなんて
Exposed in the flickering instant of a time flying too fast, wishes that cannot be reached alone
消えそうな言葉じゃ 辿り着けない
cannot be reached with fading words.
じっと瞳を凝らしても 見失ってしまう星
Even if I fix my eyes on it, it's a star I lose sight of,
誰のものにもならない 光がある
a light that belongs to no one.
口唇 確かめる 生命の灯が
The light of life confirmed on our lips
思い詰めたように 眩しいから
is as dazzling as if it were bottled up with heavy thoughts.
愛が先なのか 壊すのが先か 惑わされる
Is love first, or is destruction first? I'm bewildered.
絡み合う熱の 伝えたい真実を
The truth of intertwined heat that I want to convey—
誰から守ればいい？ キミがいつか
who should I protect it from? The feeling you wanted someday
欲しかった想いが そこにあるなら…
if it's right there...
Hey, hey! モリカリオペ 超かわいいよ！Hey, hey, hai!
Hey, hey! Mori Calliope is super cute! Hey, hey, yeah!
皆さん、の素敵な応援、ありがとう！皆さんかわいい！カリオペかわいい！Hey, hey, hey, 超元気になって盛り上げて！
Everyone, thank you for your wonderful support! Everyone is cute! Calliope is cute! Hey, hey, get super energetic and hype it up!
皆さん、Here we go! When I say Gundam, you say Psycho Gundam!
Everyone, here we go! When I say Gundam, you say Psycho Gundam!
Gundam! Gundam! Psycho Gundam! いいね、皆さん！
Gundam! Gundam! Psycho Gundam! Nice, everyone!
速過ぎる時の 瞬きに晒されて
Exposed in the flickering instant of a time flying too fast,
一人では届かない 願いなんて
wishes that cannot be reached alone
消えそうな言葉じゃ 辿り着けない
cannot be reached with fading words.
誰から守ればいい？ キミがいつか 欲しかった想いが
Who should I protect it from? The feeling you wanted someday
キミにあるから…
is inside you...
懐かしいな。
This brings back memories.
ポーズして。ポーズしてるよ。
Strike a pose. I'm posing.
カリオペかっこいい。かっこいいね。You look really cool, Kelly. Thanks.
Calliope looks cool. So cool. You look really cool, Kelly. Thanks.
どう？
How was that?
誰もが皆知ってる
Everyone knows it,
消せやしない傷を
the scars that can't be erased.
どれくらい続くの?
How much longer will this last?
もういらないよ
I don't need it anymore.
誰もが皆待ってる
Everyone is waiting,
争いのない
for a world without conflict.
日々を 戦場の
The days on the battlefield—
兵士たち 思い出してよ 今目の温もりを
soldiers, remember the warmth right before you now!
この果てしなく広い世界に
In this endless, vast world,
自分だけの地図描いて
draw your own map,
涙こらえて僕らは歩いてゆくんだ
and holding back our tears, we will keep walking.
立ち上がれ今 ほら何度でも
Stand up now, see, no matter how many times,
眠れる獅子 呼び起こして 生きてゆくんだ 明日へ
rouse the sleeping lion and live on toward tomorrow!
誰もが皆待ってる
Everyone is waiting,
一欠片の
for even a single fragment
愛を憎んでも 人ひとつ 生まれないんだよ そんなのもういらないよ
of love. Hating it won't create a single human life. I don't need things like that anymore!
この限りある時間の中で
Within this limited time,
まだ見ぬ楽園目指して
aiming for an unseen paradise,
どこまでだって僕らは歩いてゆくわ
no matter how far, we will keep walking.
振り向かないで 前だけを見て
Don't look back, look only ahead,
その身体朽ち果てるまで 生きてゆくんだ 未来へ
and until this body decays, live on toward the future!
思い出してよ 今目の温もりを
Remember the warmth right before you now,
この果てしなく広い世界の
in this endless, vast world.
In this endless, vast world,
まだ見ぬ楽園目指して
aiming for an unseen paradise,
どこまでだって僕らは歩いて
no matter how far, we will keep walking.
振り向かないで 前だけを見て
Don't look back, look only ahead,
その身体朽ち果てるまで 生きてゆくんだ 未来へ
and until this body decays, live on toward the future!
生きてゆくんだ 未来へ
Live on toward the future!
アイデン貞貞メルトダウン
[Song: Iden Teitei Meltdown]
アリ！？ナシ！？ナシ！？アリ！？
Yes!? No!? No!? Yes!?
アリ！？ナシ！？アリ！？ どっち？どっち？チャンス！チャンス！チャンス！
Ari?! Nashi?! Ari?! Which is it? Chance, chance, chance!
アリ！ナシ！ナシ！アリ！
Ari! Nashi! Nashi! Ari!
実際の感情はNo Think!
Actual feelings? No think!
気付かないフリ...?
Pretending not to notice...?
絶対的な虚実と中身
Absolute truth and falsehoods,
そうやって減っていく安置 よ なんだ
Safe spaces dwindling away just like that,
(バイバイ！ Alright！ 一級在宅 allday！)
(Bye-bye! Alright! First-class homebody all day!)
やる気の矢の持久に行っちゃったんだ
Motivation's arrow ran out of stamina.
傷の切り売り
Selling off your wounds piece by piece,
脆く叫ぶ、醜態
Screaming weakly, a disgraceful sight.
最高級の逃避行
The highest-class escape,
やがて、甘美な罠に釣られたものから救われる?
Will those caught in the sweet trap eventually be saved?
もはや正気の沙汰ではない
In this mundane world where we can no longer live sanely...
敢えて素知らぬ顔で
Boldly putting on a feigned ignorance,
身を任せるのが最適解?
is surrendering yourself the optimal solution?
言葉で飾った花束も
Even a bouquet of flowers adorned with words—
心を奪えば、本物か?
if it steals your heart, is it the real thing?
全てが染まっていくような現象にご招待
You're invited to a phenomenon where everything becomes dyed.
知らない 何壊れそうなアイデンティティ
Not knowing what identity is about to break,
生まれたばかり a sense of wonder
just born, a sense of wonder.
そのまま baby 溶けてゆく深層心理
Just like that, baby, melting deep into your psyche,
目覚め たまえ 眠れるアイツ
awaken, you sleeping fellow!
自分自身を知るための闘だ
It's a battle to know yourself.
行くところまでいってみようか ハッピーエンド?
Shall we go all the way? A happy ending?
アリ！？ナシ！？アリ！？どっち？どっち？
Ari?! Nashi?! Ari?! Which is it, which is it?
チャンス！チャンス！チャンス！アリ！ナシ！
Chance! Chance! Chance! Ari! Nashi!
ナシ！アリ！
Nashi! Ari!
自我 自我が 崩壊中！
Ego, ego is collapsing!
お散歩 超世代 兵士でおかえり
Taking a walk, returning like a super-generation soldier.
(バイバイ！ fall down！ 三流散策 weekend！)
(Bye-bye! Fall down! Third-rate stroll weekend!)
やる気を出した結果が大惨事だった
The result of trying to get motivated was a total disaster!
(しない！ ファイト一発！)
(Don't! Fight to the finish!)
ああ マジカルウルトラ スーパーミラクル
Ah, magical ultra super miracle,
抱きしめて 慰めてくれよ
embrace me and console me, yeah,
ええ そんなの 夢さ ドリームワンダーランド
such a dream is a dream wonderland!
地道 努力 コツコツ 正論マンがパンチした
Steady effort, hard work, the Mr. Righteous Man punched,
左右！ (Uh!) 右！ (Ha!) 左右！ (ワンツー！)
Left! (Uh!) Right! (Ha!) Left! (One-two!)
いらない 愛 つながり アイデンティティ
Unwanted love, connections, identity,
素直になりなさい catch on fire
Be honest, catch on fire!
わがまま baby 溶けてゆく 固定観念
Selfish baby, melting fixed ideas,
古い 答え うちなるケモノ
old answers, the inner beast,
自分自身を知るための決闘だ
it's a duel to know yourself!
白か黒かで決めろよ！(極論！)
Decide in black or white! (Extreme theory!)
0か100しかないの？(極論！)
Is it only 0 or 100? (Extreme theory!)
生きづらいぞ 世間体ね (しゃばばい！)
It's hard to live with public expectations! (Shababai!)
神様 仏様 この私にお導きを
Gods and Buddhas, guide this self of mine!
それでいいのか(YES! NO!) アイデンティティよ 目を覚ませ
Is that okay? (YES! NO!) Wake up, identity!
知りたい 愛 どこへ行く 自意識
Wanting to know love, where is self-consciousness going?
ゆりかごゆられて どんぶらこっこ
Rocked in a cradle, floating along,
このまま 眠り消えてゆく世界のエンド
in this world where sleep makes everything vanish at the end.
端っこ つかみ もがいた
Catching the edge and struggling,
知らない 何 壊れそうなアイデンティティ
not knowing what identity is about to break,
生まれたばかり a sense of wonder
just born, a sense of wonder.
そのまま baby 溶けてゆく 深層心理
Just like that, baby, melting deep into your psyche,
目覚め たまえ 眠れるアイツ
awaken, you sleeping fellow!
自分自身を知るための旅路
It's a journey to know yourself.
ひとりのようで ひとりじゃなかった
Though feeling alone, I wasn't alone;
観測上で 成り立つ 存在X
existence X established on observation!
研究対象です！
You're a research subject!
アリ！？ナシ！？アリ！？どっち？どっち？
Ari?! Nashi?! Ari?! Which is it, which is it?
チャンス！チャンス！チャンス！アリ！ナシ！
Chance! Chance! Chance! Ari! Nashi!
ナシ！アリ！
Nashi! Ari!
自我 自我が アイデンティティは 崩壊中！
Ego, ego, identity is collapsing!
I did my own backing vocals you guys, did you like them?
I shouldn't dance so much while singing!
Arigatou, unexpected, ne?
Thank you, unexpected, right?
I fucking love that anime.
Oh, I think we have a guest! Do we have a guest here?
Oh my god! Whoa!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Mori
Happy birthday dear Ca... Calli-senpai!
Happy birthday dear Ka... Calli-senpai!
Happy birthday to you
That's so nice!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
闇夜のケーキを持ってきました！
I brought a dark night cake!
やみやみ、食べたい、食べたいな！
Yami-yami, I wanna eat it, I wanna eat it!
かわいいでしょ？
Isn't it cute?
すごい！
Amazing!
カリオペ先輩仕様スペシャルワン！
Calliope-senpai's custom special one!
Wow, many special details. Yeah.
すごい、めっちゃんこ素敵！今食べますか？
So amazing, super lovely! Will you eat it now?
ああ、どうかな。まあ、実話…なんか、ライブ中あんまり食べたくないね、あの、あとで。
Ah, I wonder. Well, actually... You know, during a live, I don't really wanna eat much, you know, later on...
ああ、じゃあ、あとで食べましょうね、一緒にね！じゃあ、ちょっと、
Ah, then let's eat it later together, okay? Then, wait,
お先にね、置いときますんで、後で食べてください。
well, we'll leave it on stage, so please eat it later.
めっちゃうまそう！
It looks super delicious!
すごい！じゃ、こっちに。
Amazing! Then over here.
いいね！めっちゃんこ最高！
Nice! Super awesome!
ありがとう！Thank you for inviting me.
Thank you! Thank you for inviting me.
わあ、いぇい、いぇい！めちゃ嬉しい！どりちゃん、本当に一緒に歌いたかったからね。
Wow, yay, yay! I'm so happy! Dori-chan, I really wanted to sing together with you.
Happy birthday today!
Thank you so much! San, congratulations, you are really the birthday...
Thank you so much! Mori, congratulations, you are really the birthday...
Yes, that's right, that's right! みんな、ちゃんと言ってね。
Yes, that's right, that's right! Everyone, say it properly, okay?
すごい、みんなめっちゃんこワクワクしてるね。嬉しい。
Wow, everyone is super excited, huh? I'm so happy.
はあ、すごい。ちょっと待ってね。
Haa, amazing. Wait a second.
話してて。めっちゃんこ、なんか外まで聞こえててましたよ。
Keep talking. It was echoing all the way outside, you know.
ああ、そうだね。
Ah, that's right.
あ、ほら、んで、あの骸骨くん、あ、骸骨ちゃん。会ったことある？（笑）はじめまして。かわいいね。Nice to meet you.
Ah, look, and that skeleton-kun—ah, skeleton-chan. Have you ever met? (Laughs) Nice to meet you. Cute. Nice to meet you.
そう、踊りがめちゃ上手いよ。じゃあ、私も一緒に踊ります。
Yeah, her dancing is super good. Well, I'll dance along too.
いいね！
Nice! (Laughs)
いいね、いいね、ステキ、ステキ！すごい！Rolling, rolling, rolling, rolling!
Good, good, lovely, lovely! Amazing! Rolling, rolling, rolling, rolling!
ええ、いいね！ちょっとセクシーすぎる。
Eh, nice! A bit too sexy.
ああ、いや、見えない見えない！ちょっと待って、いや、ちょっと待って！
Ah, no, I can't look, I can't look! Wait a minute, no, wait a minute!
いや、無理無理無理！カリオペ無理よ！もう、恥ずかしすぎる！
No, no way, no way! Calliope, no way! I'm way too embarrassed!
なんかね、あの、今日は、あの、めっちゃ、あの、なんかピッチが低い曲歌いたかったけど、
Somehow, you know, today, um, super, um, like, I wanted to sing a song with a low pitch, but,
あの、なんかホロライブで、あの、誰が、あの、低い声で歌えるかなと思ってて、
um, I was thinking like, in Hololive, um, who, um, can sing with a low voice,
あの、ルイちゃん！しかり、ルイちゃん。
um, Lui-chan! Definitely Lui-chan.
Nice to meet you, yeah?
Yes, JPメンバーの中で一番低いですからね、声が。That's right.
Yes, among JP members, hers is the lowest, right? The voice. That's right.
Yeah, yeah, I decided to ask Lui to come sing with me because I wanted to sing a really low song, and she has the lowest voice that I think I know in Hololive,
besides Towa-senpai, who'll have to do maybe next time, but, but I love, uh, Lui's voice.
そう、あ、そうそうそう。あ、少々お待ちくださいね。Please wait a moment.
So, ah, yes, yes, yes. Ah, please wait a moment. Please wait a moment.
あ、You need a mic!
Ah, You need a mic! (Laughs)
そうだね、座りましょう。You need a mic!
That's right, let's sit down. You need a mic!
Oh my gosh、ちょっと忘れちゃったね。
Oh my gosh, I totally forgot.
Oh my gosh! OK, we gotta, gotta switch mics for a second.
あ、かわいい！みんなかわいい、みんなかわいくない？かわいい。
Ah, cute! Everyone is cute, aren't they all cute? Cute.
あ、ちゃんとのDeadbeatsのメンバーも超かわいいね。Thank you. Hm. Wonderful. Well, let's sing, yeah?
Ah, and all of Deadbeats are super cute too. Thank you. Hm. Wonderful. Well, let's sing, yeah?
うん、yeah. All right, I have a good song.
Mm, yeah. All right, I have a good song.
Exciting, exciting. What do you think it is, Chad?
低音曲？骸骨ちゃんも一緒にダンシング、ダンスしてくださいね。はい。
Low-song? Skeleton-chan, please dance along too, okay? Yes.
What do we sing? Oh, well, let's see, 歌いましょう。
What do we sing? Oh, well, let's see, let's sing.
BLOODY STREAM!
静寂の底から 目覚めるその柱たち
From the depths of silence, those awakening pillars
時を超え 深紅の血潮が
transcending time, the crimson bloodstream
立ち上がる 勇気を引き合わせる
rises up, bringing together courage
受け継ぐ愛を 定めと呼ぶなら
If the love passed down is called destiny,
微笑む目で 次の手を
with a smiling gaze, take the next move
闇を欺いて 刹那を交わして
Deceiving the darkness, sharing fleeting moments
刃すり抜け 奴らの隙を突け 貫いた想いが未来を開く
Slipping past blades, striking their openings—piercing thoughts open the future!
Like a Bloody Storm 熱く Like a Bloody Stone
Like a Bloody Storm, passionately like a Bloody Stone
血脈に刻まれた因縁に
In the karma etched into our veins,
浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆 握りしめ
the unyielding bond of pride emerges, clutching it tight
闇をあざむいて 刹那をかわして
Deceiving the darkness, sharing fleeting moments,
刃すりぬけ 奴らの隙をつき
slipping past blades, striking their openings
つらぬいいた想いが 未来をひらく
Piercing thoughts open up the future!
Like a Bloody Storm 熱く Like a Bloody Stone
Like a Bloody Storm, passionately like a Bloody Stone
血脈に刻まれた因縁に
In the karma etched into our veins,
浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆 握りしめて
the unyielding bond of pride emerges, clutching it tight
握りしめて 素敵！
Clutching it tight, how wonderful!
こんな素敵な曲歌ってるからね！
We're singing such a wonderful song!
Yeah!
満ちる力に 滲む痛みに
With overflowing power and blurring pain,
打ち付ける鼓動は証
the pounding beat is proof,
友の声
a friend's voice.
滲んだ痛みと 生き抜く意味を
With blurring pain and the meaning to survive,
交わしながら
while exchanging them,
お前の前へ
before you.
カリ！
Calli!
お前の意思が 夜明けを導く
Your will guides the dawn,
まだ許せぬほどの けがれさえも
even the unforgivable stains.
光射す丘へ 灼熱の空
To the hill where light shines, the scorching sky,
魂がぶつかり合うたびへ
every time our souls collide,
悲しみに塗られた 未来を救え
save the future stained in sorrow.
Like a Bloody Soul 燃やせ Like a Bloody Star
Like a Bloody Soul, burn like a Bloody Star!
突き切る風を断ち その先へ
Cut through the biting wind, moving beyond,
恐れずに何ひとつ戸惑いはあるまい
without fear or a single hesitation!
流れの中
In the flow of it all,
共鳴する 運命の波紋
the ripples of fate resonate.
心に…
Within our hearts...
闇をあざむいて
Deceiving the darkness,
切なさを交わして
exchanging our anguish,
刃すり抜け 奴らの隙をつけ
slip past the blades, strike their openings!
貫いた想いが 未来を開く
The piercing feelings open up the future.
Like a Bloody Storm 燃えろ Like a Bloody Stone
Like a Bloody Storm, burn like a Bloody Stone!
血脈に刻まれた 幾年日に
In the eternal days carved into our bloodline,
湧き上がる 消えない誇りの絆
the surging, unextinguishable bonds of pride—
握りしめて
grasp them tight!
ジャオ！
Chao!
いいね！いいジャオポーズ！
Nice! Great Chao pose!
素敵！パーフェクト！
Wonderful! Perfect!
いややっぱりめちゃめちゃ上手かった！
Man, you were really, really good!
いやでも今日2回目！Second time is 3D collaboration.
Yeah, but this is our second time! Second time in 3D collaboration.
そうだね！First time is マイクロ…
That's right! The first time was the Mycro...
いじめっ子莉々華！
Bully Ririka!
Yes yes yes! 超楽しかった！ 今日はお呼びいただきましてありがとうございました！
Yes, yes, yes! It was so much fun! Thank you so much for inviting me today!
いやいやこちらこそ超楽しかった本当に！
No, no, I had so much fun too, truly!
これからも続くのでね、 Please enjoy!
This will continue from now on, so please enjoy!
はい、エンジョイします！あとでね、ケーキ一緒に食べよう！
Yes, I will enjoy it! Later on, let's eat cake together!
はい！これね、食べましょう！そう、食べましょうめちゃめちゃ美味そうから。
Yes! Let's eat this! Yeah, let's eat it, it looks super delicious.
Have a nice day!
It looks so good today!
Thank you, I'll do my best!
And they'd be... See you!
Bye bye!
Bye bye, dead beat! Yes!
Bye bye, Deadbeats! Yes!
じゃあ、またの機会ね！
Well then, until next time!
See you!
Bye-bye!
There goes Ririka.
I knew that she was going to sing that song so good.
I knew that she was going to sing that song so well.
I knew it!
I knew it, she like wasn't super super familiar with it before,
I knew it, she wasn't super familiar with it before,
but like she knocked it out of the park.
but she knocked it out of the park.
I must have been lonely, but that's okay.
I must seem a bit lonely, but that's okay.
I'm going to show you something. I want to show you a thing.
You both slayed it.
Thank you so much, you guys are very sweet.
Really amazing, indeed. That was straight fire.
Her voice is beautiful.
Agreed, she's so amazing.
Um, so we're going to watch something so I can sit down for a second, right?
So, we're going to watch something so I can sit down for a second, right?
Uh, we're going to watch a video.
We're going to watch a video.
Now, you guys know it's my birthday, right?
It's Mori Day.
You can tweet out #HappyMoriDay with your screenshots and to show your appreciation for your Mori, if you'd like.
You can tweet out #HappyMoriDay with your screenshots to show your appreciation for Mori, if you'd like.
Should you be so inclined, right?
Um, if you'd like to.
If you'd like to.
So, additionally, there's something I want to show you guys.
Additionally, there's something I want to show you guys.
It's a video, a video of things you can buy.
It's a video of things you can buy.
That's right. Do you guys want to buy things?
Geikotsu-chan, hora mite, issho ni miyo.
Skeleton-chan, look, let's watch together.
Check it out, everyone.
Tired of owning...
Useless items you'll never use,
because you got lured in by that low, low price of 19.99?
Well, fear not, because on today's shopping program, Shop Till You Drop Dead, featuring Calliope Mori,
none of our items are 19.99.
Oh, no!
Get ready to feast your eyes on some premium tier items you'll literally want to gouge your eyes out if you don't own them out of sheer FOMO
and additional existential dread of the emptiness of your life without them, you need these items.
You need that!
Why not get a sick poster of your one and only boy to display it at work
and assert your dominance over your friends?
That's right, folks! Mori Calliope's Special Birthday Poster features Mori Calliope rocking out at a concert she definitely did, with an outfit she definitely wore!
You won't want to miss this premium item 'cause once it's gone, it's gone for good. Fuck you scalpers, get it now!
Ever wanted to bathe yourself in sweet smelling, delicious purple liquid?
Well, I sure can't relate,
but if you do, then you better get your hands on this special dual set of bath bombs from Mori Calliope's favorite premium Underworld Onsen!
They come in two scents: Mori Rose and Death Sensei Purple Mist.
Get yours today, you smell like shit!
Thirsty? Surrounded by hot e-girls? Who the hell isn't?
But too bad for you, that's no e-girl on your mug, it's your dad! Your Mori dad!
With an exclusive design by Mori Calliope father to all, you'll be feeling like number one as you sip your stress, anxiety, and existential dread away.
Don't miss your chance to grab it, dummy!
Lil' swag lord...
Plush comes with one outfit. Design details differ from final version, no trades are guaranteed...
So what are you waiting for, deadbeat? If you get the whole set, a limited number of deadbeats will get a hand-signed postcard.
They're gonna sell out fast 'cause I really like my hand, but never fear, if you buy the full set, you get a duplicated autograph postcard.
Remember, deadbeats, shop until you're dead beats! Get it? Deadbeats! Like the name of the fans!
Yo, shut the fuck up, no one's laughing at that shit.
Wait, Mori, no, I'm sorry! Please don't beat me! Stop! Please don't beat me! Stop that shit out! No more! Mori, please pick the- oh, god! Ow, I hurt- oh, I feel pain!
silly bakka, silly ba-
シリアスashit, lemme shake it up
Serious as shit, lemme shake it up
do what i want, shit, gotta reckon ya
got a thirst for the worst look in’馬鹿なcheap-ass
Got a thirst for the worst lookin' stupid cheap-ass
silly bakka, silly ba
silly ass-looking shit, gotta shake it up
wanna be lookin’ freaks, all they do is talk
Wanna be lookin' freaks, all they do is talk
getcha head out ya ass, like, what you got, huh?
毎回毎回神頼み
Praying to the gods every single time
免罪せんぞそんな奴に
There's no absolution for someone like that
あー、もう情状酌量の余地なし
Ah, there's no room for extenuating circumstances
即死刑、はい
Immediate death penalty, yep
地獄までお迎え なさ い
Be escorted all the way to hell
今 すぐ に お 迎え なさ い
Be escorted right now
メラメラ burning all day
Mera mera, burning all day
真夏の楽園
A midsummer paradise
メラメラ凍かされて
Mera mera, frozen over
灰になるまで
Until turning to ashes
メロメロにさせて
Mero mero, make me fall for you
さあ踊り狂っちゃって
Now dance like you're crazy
火炙り パラダイス
A fiery paradise
go up and down
silly bakka, silly ba
シリアスashit, lemme shake it up
Serious as shit, lemme shake it up
do what i want, shit, you know what i got
might be the pinnacle of cynical but first keep the mic hot
and may i just remind you
act a fool, death’s gotta fine you
Act a fool, Death's gotta fine you
eh, dum-di-dum-dum-de
da-da-dum-de
c-a-double l, you already know
C-A-double-L, you already know
scythe at the ready, slow and steady, give ’em a show
Scythe at the ready, slow and steady, give 'em a show
they wanna get real close, can’t learn to let go!
They wanna get real close, can't learn to let go!
try ’n dance with her, answer to, look out below
Try 'n dance with her, answer to, look out below
slaying to the beat, paint the street redder than rose
and slam ’em back ’til the sun rise and heaven’s closed
And slam 'em back 'til the sun rise and heaven's closed
sleepin’ ’til the next night, y’all know where we go
Sleepin' 'til the next night, y'all know where we go
believe i still keep the tight shinigami flow
alright?
メラメラ burning all day
Mera mera, burning all day
真夏の楽園
A midsummer paradise
メラメラ凍かされて
Mera mera, frozen over
灰になるまで
Until turning to ashes
メロメロにさせて
Mero mero, make me fall for you
冥土の土産に舞う
Dancing as a farewell gift to the underworld
that is all about
ほらまだまだ足らない
Look, it's still not enough
spent all day beneath the sun, sun, sun, sun
sub is blasting’ out, dan-dan-dan-dan
Sub is blastin' out, dan-dan-dan-dan
i don’t care, sing out, la-la-la-la
I don't care, sing out, la-la-la-la
one night this time, you don’t gotta run, run
One night this time, you don't gotta run, run
Right here, look. Look at all the nice things you get, depending on the store you buy it from.
There are like all kinds of different little things that you can get.
Um, in addition, the only way to get them all is to buy the Blu-ray many, many times, I don't know.
In addition, the only way to get them all is to buy the Blu-ray many, many times, I don't know.
Um, if if you'd like to, you certainly can,
If you'd like to, you certainly can,
because like I said, if you buy this Blu-ray, oh, my dreams come true.
Yay, Mori store! Yay, Mori store! Yay!
Um, yeah, it would make me really, really happy because I'm super proud of uh of this of this release.
It would make me really, really happy because I'm super proud of this release.
Um, so yeah, check out the Blu-ray.
So yeah, check out the Blu-ray.
And don't go anywhere because I still have one big announcement, a couple announcements, but one really big announcement at the end of the stream, so don't go anywhere, okay?
And don't go anywhere because I still have a big announcement... a couple of announcements, but one really big announcement at the end of the stream, so don't go anywhere, okay?
We still got more to do. But yeah, buy the Blu-ray, it would make it would make me really happy.
We still got more to do. But yeah, buy the Blu-ray, it would make me really happy.
Yeah, that would be really great.
Um, another really big show might happen someday. Well, I guess the surprise is kind of ruined,
Another really big show might happen someday. Well, I guess the surprise is kind of ruined,
but just kidding, here it is.
Daijoubu, you didn't see anything. You didn't see anything. You didn't see anything. You saw nothing.
It's fine, you didn't see anything. You didn't see anything. You didn't see anything. You saw nothing.
Oh god, da- no, don't look there. Don't look there!
Oh god, no, don't look there. Don't look there!
No, no, no, no, no. It's fine. You pretend like you didn't—pretend like you didn't see anything. There's still another—there's still another announcement, okay?
No, no, no, no, no. It's fine. Pretend like you didn't—pretend like you didn't see anything. There's still another announcement, okay?
Just just pretend like you didn't see—I don't know what you're talking about.
Just pretend like you didn't see... I don't know what you're talking about.
Hey, I think someone's here. Oh my gosh, what is this?
Perhaps the sound of a phone that's about to ring?
電話、電話かな？電話ありますね？
A phone? Is a phone ringing? There's a phone, right?
ほら見て、We have a phone over here. Isn't that great?
Look, we have a phone over here. Isn't that great?
Uh, it would be awesome if it was to ring at some point.
It would be awesome if it were to ring at some point.
Oh, it's ringing.
Oh my gosh, no way! All right, let me see if I can grab it. Watch this.
Moshimoshi? IRyS, Kelly, I heard you're lonely at a karaoke booth by yourself on your birthday. Is the phone okay?
Yeah, no, I can hear you perfectly well. I don't don't worry about it, it's fine. It's fine. Hold on. Let me hold on.
Yeah, no, I can hear you perfectly well. Don't worry about it, it's fine. It's fine. Hold on. Let me...
Let me just t-pose real quick.
大丈夫かな？
Are you okay?
Oh, hello. Okay, sorry, I can hear you perfectly now, IRyS. Hey, what's going on?
Hey, I heard you were lonely and I was wondering if you wanted a visit from a certain Nephilim or so.
I'm not lonely. But but wait, no no no no.
I'm not lonely. But wait, no, no, no, no.
You don't want me to come? No, please, I don't have to come, you know.
No, no, no, I want to sing with you!
IRyS, please come here. Yeah, let's karaoke party. I'll run there right now. I'll teleport there, yeah.
Are you sure you can run? You have legs to run with?
Are you sure you can run? Do you have legs to run with?
Uh, there'll be something. I'm sure I might go too fast. I might lose some dimension on my body, but...
Okay, well, good luck. I'm just going to go ahead and put the phone away then. All right, I'm hanging up now, bye.
There it goes. I put the phone away. Hi.
Okay, it looks like IRyS is going to come and join us. We're going to maybe sing together. Does that sound cool?
All right. Well, let's wait and see when she's going to be here. Me and Geikotsu-chan are waiting.
虹色の回廊に 無数の言葉たち
In the rainbow-colored corridor, countless words
半分だけでも ここなら進んで行ける
Even if it's only half, if it's here, I can keep moving forward
突然のメロディ また加速して行く
A sudden melody accelerates once again
心を掴んだ ひとひらの影も消し去る
It captured my heart and erased even the shadow of a single petal
眼差シ キラキラ あまり大きくない道でもいい
Eyes sparkling brightly, even a path that isn't very big is fine
そして
And then,
駆け出す 飛び込む 奇跡へ
Running and diving toward the miracle
見上げる 手を振る 光へ
Looking up and waving hands toward the light
止まらない気持ちを繋いで行く
Connecting unstoppable feelings
リフレクティア
Reflectia
揺らめく 近付く 明日へ
Towards a shimmering, approaching tomorrow
奏でる 夢見る 未来へ
Towards a musical, dreaming future
まっさらな空どこまでも連れて
Taking me anywhere under a pristine sky
涙の終わり 合図に
As a signal to the end of tears
無意識のメロディ 風になるように
An unconscious melody, like becoming the wind
記憶の隙間が 一瞬を求め続ける
The gaps in memory continue to demand a single moment
まどろみ フワフワ 踏み出せるならきっと大丈夫
Illusions floating softly, if you can take a step forward, it will surely be alright
そして
And then,
重ねる 促す 願いを
Overlapping and urging wishes
導く 追い越す 時間を通れば浮かんでき
Guiding and overtaking time...
虹色の回廊に
In the rainbow-colored corridor,
無数の言葉たち
countless words...
半分だけでも
Even if it's only half,
ここならば 進んでいける
if it's here, we can keep moving forward.
突然のメロディ
A sudden melody
また加速していく
accelerates once more.
心を掴んだ
Capturing our hearts,
ひとひらの影も消し去る
it erases even a single shadow.
まなざし キラキラ
Gazes sparkling bright,
あまり大きくない道でもいいね
even a modest path is fine.
そして 駆け出す 飛び込む
And then, running out, leaping in,
奇跡へ 見上げる 手を振る
toward a miracle, looking up, waving our hands,
光へ 止まらない気持ちをつないでいく
toward the light, connecting feelings that won't stop.
リフレクティア 揺らめく 近づく
Reflectia, flickering, drawing closer,
明日へ 奏でる 夢見る
toward tomorrow, playing melodies, dreaming,
未来へ まっさらな空 どこまでも連れて
toward the future, taking us anywhere in the pristine sky,
涙の終わり 愛すに
turning the end of tears into love...
Fading sharing yet say lovely
秘密のメロディ
A secret melody
風になるように
becoming like the wind,
記憶の隙間が 一瞬間を求め続ける
the gaps in our memories keep searching for a single moment.
まぼろし フワ フワ
Phantoms drifting softly,
出せるなら大丈夫 きっと大丈夫
if we can let them out, it'll be alright, surely alright.
そして 重ねる 促す
And then, layering, prompting,
願いを 導く 追い越す
guiding our wishes, overtaking time,
時間を ガラスに通せば 浮かんでくる
if we pass it through glass, it floats up.
螺旋の模様 数える
Counting the spiral patterns,
束ねる 想いを 広げる 彩る 笑顔を
bundling our feelings, spreading them, coloring our smiles.
透明な空 包まれる度に 生まれ変わって行くから
Every time we're wrapped in the transparent sky, we're reborn anew.
浮感 少しの空想に
Floating sensation, into a slight fantasy,
いつか明かしたい秘密
a secret we want to reveal someday.
いつか 打ち明けた硬い秘密
A rigid secret confessed someday,
流れて 描いて 開いて 映して 鳴らして 回って
flowing, drawing, opening, reflecting, sounding, spinning round.
小さな嘘さへ 指の先を 通り過ぎる
Even small lies pass right by our fingertips.
隔てて 壊して 走って 変えて 満たして
Partitioning, breaking, running, changing, filling up,
歌って 淡くて 遠い 君を救い出し 反射したら
singing, faintly, rescuing you from afar, once it reflects—
駆け出す 飛び込む
running out, leaping in,
奇跡へ 見上げる 手を振る
toward a miracle, looking up, waving our hands,
光へ 織りなす 軌跡 私を呼ぶ
toward the light, weaving a trajectory that calls my name.
リフレクティア 揺らめく 近づく
Reflectia, flickering, drawing closer,
明日へ 奏でる 夢見る
toward tomorrow, playing melodies, dreaming,
未来へ まっさらな空 どこまでも連れて
toward the future, taking us anywhere in the pristine sky,
限りなく舞い上がるよ
soaring boundlessly upward.
Fading sharing yet say lovely
Tear did Falling are reed feel
Tears falling, our real feel
Yeah, jeez,
together, together, together.
Just kidding, I'm not trying to tire you out.
We still have another song to sing.
What could that other song be?
Something really hype.
So we should sing a really hype anime song.
Such as one that like everybody knows and gets really excited about, like um...
Like they want to... they want to shout the first part of the song.
Ah, that song! Yeah, the one that starts with a G, G, G, G...
Shibouou!
Igima show COLORS!
Let's go!
自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな 瞬間は いつも すぐそばに…
jibunwo sekaisaemo kaeteshimaesouna shunkanwa itsumo sugu sobani...
隠せぬ 苛立ちと 立ち尽くす 自分を 見つめ 迷いながら 悩みながら 悔やみながら 決めればいいさ 君がくれた 言葉ひとつ 戸惑いは 消え去り からっぽだった 僕の部屋に 光が射した
kakusenu iradachito tachitsukusu jibunwo mitasemei mayoinagara nayaminagara kuyaminagara kimerebaiisa kimiwoguretakotoba hitotsu todowaikiesari karappodattabokunoheyani hikarigasasita
見上げた大空が 青く澄み切って行く 閉ざした 窓を 開くことを 決めた 自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな 瞬間は いつも すぐそばに…
miagetaootoraga aokumikitteiku tozasitamadowohirakukoto kimetasjibunwo sekaisaemo kaeteshimaesouna shunkanwa itsumo sugu sobani...
満たせぬ日々に 在るはずの答を 探して… 朝陽に独り 柔らかな声に 振り返れば 眩しい陽射しの中 ふと君が微笑む 閉ざした窓が 開きそうになる
mitasenuniichininiaruhazunokotewo sagaseite... asayinihitori yawarakanakoeni hurikaereba mabushiiyishisinaka hutokimigamiemu tozasitamadowohirakusouninaru
自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな 存在は 目の前に…
jibunwo sekaisaemo kaeteshimaesouna sonzaiwa menomaeni...
見上げた大空が 青く澄み切って行く 閉ざした 窓を 開くことを 決めた 自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな 瞬感を 感じる今ここに…
miagetaootoraga aokumikitteiku tozasitamadowohirakukoto kimetasjibunwo sekaisaemo kaeteshimaesouna shunkanwo kanjiruimakokoni...
光へと 両手を伸ばして… 心を吹き抜ける 空の色香る風
hikarieto ryotewonobashite... kokorowofukinukeru Sorano irokaorukaze
自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな 瞬間は いつも すぐそばに… 満たせぬ日々に 在るはずの答を 探して…
jibunwo sekaisaemo kaeteshimaesouna shunkanwa itsumo sugu sobani... mitasenuniichininiaruhazunokotewo sagaseite...
朝陽に独り 柔らかな声に 振り返れば 眩しい陽射しの中 ふと君が微笑む 閉ざした窓が 開きそうになる
asayinihitori yawarakanakoeni hurikaereba mabushiiyishisinaka hutokimigamiemu tozasitamadowohirakusouninaru
自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな 存在は 目の前に…
jibunwo sekaisaemo kaeteshimaesouna sonzaiwa menomaeni...
見上げた大空が 青く澄み切って行く 閉ざした 窓を 開くことを 決めた 自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな 瞬感を 感じる今ここに…
miagetaootoraga aokumikitteiku tozasitamadowohirakukoto kimetasjibunwo sekaisaemo kaeteshimaesouna shunkanwo kanjiruimakokoni...
光へと 両手を伸ばして… 心を吹き抜ける 空の色香る風
hikarieto ryotewonobashite... kokorowofukinukeru Sorano irokaorukaze
What is going on?
That was a perfect camera shot, wasn't it?
It was a perfect meme ending to a perfect meme song.
Yeah.
Very nice.
That was fun.
That was a good time. Thank you so much.
Thank you, Calli, for inviting...
No, actually I invited myself. What am I talking about?
Yeah, she's kind of flying around right now, like...
Like she owns the place. Oi, oi, oi!
What happens if I lie down?
Let's find out.
Oh god! Oh god!
Wow, she's clipping through the... Oh, Lord!
God, she's going to see something yaiba.
Ganbare, ganbare!
We knew this would happen.
You want to T-pose and fix it?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Well, before that, can I kick you once?
No! Stop! Stop it! Stop!
Feel the leg!
Oi, oi, oi, Omaetta!
Hey!
All righty, please fix me.
Kami-sama.
T-pose?
Little T-pose for IRyS, as she gets fixed.
Anyway, they're gonna they're gonna fix IRyS.
Anyway, they're gonna fix IRyS.
They're gonna fix her. She got a little crazy. It's fine.
We did this to ourselves.
This was our bad, but it's fine.
It was worth it to watch to watch IRyS clip into the ground, so, and have her kick me. It's fine.
It was worth it to watch IRyS clip into the ground and have her kick me. It's fine.
It's fine.
It's all good in the neighborhood.
Hold on, she's getting fixed now.
You guys want to hear a joke?
I want to hear it.
I don't I don't have any joke.
I don't have any jokes.
Sorry.
I just asked, I was just asking, I wasn't going to tell a joke, I was just asking if you wanted to hear one.
I just asked—I was just asking. I wasn't going to tell a joke, I was just asking if you wanted to hear one.
It's fine.
There she is.
IRyS! IRyS!
Oh wait,
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
Okay. Anyway,
Oh, someone's calling!
Hey!
Hold on a minute. Who's this?
Moshi moshi?
Moshi moshi? Moshi, moshi?
Moshi moshi? Moshi moshi? Moshi moshi?
Daijoubu? Daijoubu desu.
Moshi moshi?
Kayo be desu.
Dareka iru?
Must be a prank call. Somebody's there.
Happy birthday!
Oh, oh, oh, oh! Hold on a minute.
I would like to inform you guys have 10 minutes remaining until you uh get the get the air out of this car. I'm kidding. I'm going to beat you for that, Baelz.
I would like to inform you guys have 10 minutes remaining until you get the air out of this car. I'm kidding. I'm going to beat you for that, Baelz.
Happy birthday!
Thank you, Bae! Thank you, Bae! Thank you, Bae! I appreciate you.
Hey Bae.
What are you doing? Hey Bae, how do you like me in this form, Bae?
Oh no! Oh no, I disappeared into into the ground again. Are you covering you?
Oh no! Oh no, I disappeared into the ground again! Are you covering you?
Oh wait, I don't know. She's swimming now.
Oh, it's okay. I'm making the the same pose that Kaela-kun made when she was flirting with Shinjuku. You can't you can't do that.
Oh, it's okay. I'm making the same pose that Kaela-kun made when she was flirting with Shinjuku.
You can't say you can't say something like that. Sorry. You're uh, you're...
You can't say something like that. Sorry. You're uh...
Anyway, happy birthday, Kaela! Thank you, Bae!
Hey, you know what, when you do a VTuber collab, it might be something like...
I'm doing great. Thank you for making some time to call. Yeah.
Of course! Anytime for you. I was so excited to see...
I have a question for you, Bae. Little birthday question.
What do you want to see me do this year? It could be anything.
What do I want to see you do this year? Oh, that's a good question. Yeah.
I want to see you. Wait, is this like a promise that you'll do it?
Uh kind of. We'll see. That depends. Depends on some factors.
I see. Um
As as your sister, I actually would want to see you take an actual break. Oh.
As your sister, I actually would want to see you take an actual break. Oh.
I was I was waiting for it. I would like to see you...
I was waiting for it. I would like to see you...
That's what I would like you to see...
I appreciate that. Thank you. Hold on, I'm T-posing. I'm T-posing. Thank you.
I thought it was going to be something cool like like oh we should or like maybe you should learn to break dance or something. But you know what? You're saying...
I thought it was going to be something cool like, like, oh, we should or like maybe you should learn to breakdance or something. But you know what? You're saying...
No, okay, look, you said, okay, that was my sisterly answer.
Um... If... Okay. What's something that I would want to see you do this year? Something cool. Let's see. Um...
You know what? I would actually want to see you try and do a oh, we should learn how to do a freeze together.
You know what? I would actually want to see you try and do a—oh, we should learn how to do a freeze together.
A freeze?
What's that?
Um it's a breakdancing move. It's when like you do like a breakdancing move and then you freeze in like a in like a position.
Yeah?
Yeah? Yeah. Oh, okay. Yeah, yeah, definitely. I mean that sounds cool. Wait, so like you mean like a super cool like Matrix kind of thing? Like maybe like we we swivel on our heads and then like stop.
I think we can fix it.
Yeah, I think yatta!
Okay, the phone is fixed.
Oh, okay. Yeah, you said you wanted to you want to freeze together?
What's a freeze?
A freeze? A freeze is like when you like stop it's like a pose, but like you're suspending yourself off the ground. It's like a like a breakdancing pose.
A freeze? A freeze is like when you like stop—it's like a pose, but like you're suspending yourself off the ground. It's like a breakdancing pose.
Yeah, something like that. That's kind of advanced. But like there's things like a baby freeze, I think that's the first thing beginner breakdancers try and learn.
Cool.
Yeah.
I'm down. All right, then then let's do it. I mean if we ever do like a big 3D cast like live performance or something, I want to try a freeze with you.
I'm down. All right, then let's do it. I mean, if we ever do like a big 3D cast like live performance or something, I want to try a freeze with you.
Yeah, oh. Yeah, I don't know how to... I...
Wait, you don't know how to do it? Wait, you don't know how to do it?
I don't... It's been a very long time. Then how are we going to... Our butt is not like it used to be, okay? All right, all right. Well, I'll give you some time to learn and then I'll...
learn as well, okay?
Okay.
Oh my god, that'd be so much fun.
My heart stopped when I heard Laku-in earlier.
Oh, see, I thought of you. I thought of you singing that song, yeah,
'cause you know, we're all, you know, Yashi gang here, so.
Yeah.
Yeah, that that makes me really happy.
Yeah, that makes me really happy.
Well, speaking of songs that I'm doing,
what would you All right, I'm gonna give you the ability to ask me for like a dance move or pose request for the next songs that I'm gonna sing. You don't know which songs they are, but
oof, I'll insert it. But even if I'm singing a sad slow one, if you want me to do the worm, I'll do it. Don't choose that, by the way. Oof.
I'll insert it. But even if I'm singing a sad slow one, if you want me to do the worm, I'll do it. Don't choose that, by the way.
All right.
uh maybe perhaps ne-
Um, maybe perhaps...
Okay, there's Okay, I would like to see a pepper grinder move in there.
What is that? What is that? I'll like you
Okay, so put your two hands in front of you. One, and then pretend you're grinding pepper.
Yeah! Pepper grinder!
That's actually That's pretty cool. Okay, I'll do that. All right, I'll do I'll do your pepper grinder.
Yeah, do the pepper grinder. And I'd like to see Holder squat for a song.
Squat? Okay, yeah, whatever you want, Bae. All right, sure, squat.
I'll do it for you.
All right, well, I got to I got to get going. You see these eyebags I've got under my eye? They're from you. But But I love you very much.
All right, well, I got to get going. You see these eyebags I've got under my eye? They're from you. But... But I love you very much.
I love you too.
Happy birthday, Kelly.
Thank you for the birthday wishes. You're the best, Bae!
Yay, the best. I'll talk to you later.
You're the best. I'll talk to you later.
Talk to you later, Bae. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye. I'm glad you were there.
Glad you were there. I'm still here. Bye, Bae.
There we go. There we go. That was That was Bae. Bae gave me a call on my birthday.
Wasn't that sweet? Wasn't it sweet, Iris?
Yeah!
It was very sweet. Sorry, I'm I'm probably either in the ground or invisible right now. It's okay. She's become a ghost, but she's still among us. Don't chat. Never mind.
All right. Well, I wonder if somebody else will call.
他の誰か電話するかな 誰が電話するのかな
I wonder if someone else will call. Who could be calling?
Oh my gosh, someone's calling! Someone's calling! Someone's calling! All right, let's go pick up the phone again.
Let's see what happens.
I got it. Oh, it worked!
Moshi-moshi? ｷﾃｨｷﾃｨもしもし♪ きゃらわわー きゃらわわー
Moshi-moshi? (Japanese karaoke singing)
It's Wawa!
Kiara!
Wawaland!
Hello! What's up? Oh, you got like a super special themed karaoke room?
I do! I wanted to do something special this year, you know?
Oh my god, what? Eh, but it's like, normally you get these super boring karaoke rooms if you go to karaoke, you gotta pay extra for the special ones. So how much did you pay for the special
Oh my god, what? Eh, but it's like, normally you get these super boring karaoke rooms if you go to karaoke, you gotta pay extra for the special ones. So how much did you pay for the special one?
You don't want to know, Kiara, you don't want to know how much I paid. But you know what, I'm happy.
Twelve? It sometimes you gotta treat yourself to something nice.
That's true, that's true, you know what, that's that's the spice. It's the spice of life, honestly, that I get to do this kind of stuff. I'm really happy, I'm lucky, you know?
Yay! Happy birthday, Kawg-i.
Oh, thanks so much, Kiara. I appreciate you calling in to wish me a happy birthday.
I got to wish you a happy birthday too. I have it in my calendar.
Oh, yeah, thank you. Well, it's still a long time to go, but I was so surprised when I realized it, wait, what? Kelly's birthday already? No, what? It felt like just yesterday when you had your last one. I know, time really flies.
Well, I'm gonna eat lots and lots of KFP on your birthday.
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy!
Okay, but I would prefer like a cake that looks like fried chicken, but it's actually a cake, you know, those fake cakes.
Okay, but I would prefer uh like a a cake that looks like fried chicken, but it's actually a cake, you know, those fake cakes.
That is a real thing. People do know how to do that. Yeah. That's crazy.
Well, I have a question for you, Wawa. Uh what do you want to see me do this year?
This year in general? Yeah, don't say take a break because Bae said take a break.
I want you to realize some plans that you have on the you know, what do you call it? Backburner? Or like, not backburner, I don't know, but
I want you to realize some plans that you have on the uh you know, what do you call it? Backburner? Or like, not backburner, I don't know, but...
Oh, yeah. Plans that you have had since like maybe a year or so?
Yeah, just make them a reality this year.
You know what I mean? I think I know what you mean.
Wink wink wonk wonk wink wink wonk wonk.
I like that idea. Okay, well you've inspired me you've inspired me now, Kiara. Okay, I'll do it. I'll do it.
Just do it! Just do it!
Can you give me a like with the hand poses like, you know, walking around and then with the finger onto the hand, just
Oh, yeah. Wait, hold on. Finger onto the hand, just do it. And maybe you can take the props off. Yeah, that's okay. That's okay.
Just do it! Don't let your dreams be dreams! Just do it!
Something like that. I'll do it too. I'll do whatever.
You should you should do it too. Hey, also, you get a request for the next song that I'm singing. What kind of like dance move or pose do you want to see me do?
Do you know like roughly what the Vogue dance style is?
Um, can you give me an example? Vogue?
I think Oh, hi Iris! That's the first word I heard.
Oh, hi Kiara! No! I was like, hi Kiara!
I'm here! I'm here! I'm invisible!
What kind of Vogue, too?
You know how to vogue?
What is that?
You don't know?
Well, it's kind of— I mean, there's like several parts to voguing.
But I think like what I want to see you do is like over your head,
But I think what I want to see you do is, like, over your head—
like frantically, move your arms over your head, like, you know,
like, swirl and twirl and, and then—
like swirl and twirl, and then—
one hand to the left, one to the right and so,
dansa no kata, vogue shitemasuka?
"dansa no kata," do you vogue?
Oh, she don't know, she don't know yet.
Oh, she doesn't know. She doesn't know yet.
Yeah, kind of copy, kind of copy what she's doing. Oh yeah, oh yeah, she's still doing it!
Yeah, kind of copy what she's doing. Oh yeah, she's still doing it!
Yeah, she is a pro dancer after all.
Yeah, yeah, if you could vogue together with your dancer, doing the, maybe during every chorus, vogue.
Yeah, if you could vogue together with your dancer during every chorus, vogue.
Okay, every chorus? Every chorus.
All right, I'll I'll try. I can keep up.
All right, I'll try. I can keep up.
I will as much as I can.
I will. Yoroshiku!
Yoroshikune!
Yoroshiku ne!
Oh gosh, she's giving me a hard one.
All right, I'll do my best. Thanks, Kuruwa.
All right, I'll do my best. Thanks, Kiara!
Have fun! All right, dancing Kiara, fun!
Have fun! All right, dancing Kiara, have fun!
Yeah.
Oh, hold on one second, everybody. We're going to fix Iris for a second, and I'm going to put away the phone real quick.
Hold on one second, everybody. We're going to fix IRyS for a second, and I'm going to put away the phone.
I love you Kiara, bye! I love you Kiara, bye!
I love you, Kiara! Bye! Bye, Kiara! Bye!
Here we go. We're fixing Iris. She doesn't need to be fixed in my opinion, but that's okay, but
Here we go. We're fixing IRyS. She doesn't need to be fixed in my opinion, but that's okay.
I'm perfect the way I am.
Exactly.
Hold on, let me try the vogue thing.
Yeah, you're doing it! You're doing it! You're doing it!
I see it!
I'm trying.
It's beautiful.
Thank you. Arigato. Thank you. Thank you very much gakuchan.
Thank you. Arigato. Thank you very much, Gakuts-chan.
Thank you. Gakutschan is very cute.
She's scared of me though, I think.
Oh no, I don't think so.
I don't think so. She's just a little shy, but she's very outgoing around me. Yeah.
Okay. Cool, cool, cool.
Well, I wonder what we should do after this. Here, let me sit down for a second. I still have a couple songs I want to sing you guys.
Well, I wonder what we should do after this. Let me sit down for a second. I still have a couple songs I want to sing for you guys.
I want to sing some more songs.
Um, I'll do my best. We got some emotional ones in there too.
I'll do my best. We got some emotional ones in there, too.
Oh boy.
Oh man. And also we have some announcements, so don't go anywhere. But I really hope that you guys have enjoyed the show so far. I know that this is a lot more like casual and like cozy and whatnot. It's not like a really big grand showcase or anything like that. But I think that's okay.
Oh man. And also, we have some announcements, so don't go anywhere. But I really hope that you guys have enjoyed the show so far. I know that this is a lot more casual and cozy and whatnot. It's not a really big grand showcase or anything, but I think that's okay.
You know, you guys always tell me that I should have more fun, um, you know, just having a good time singing and worry less about like how high quality everything is all the time and stress myself out over it, you know?
You guys always tell me that I should have more fun, just having a good time singing and worry less about how high quality everything is all the time and stress myself out over it, you know?
And fixed!
She's fixed.
Speaking of which, looking very high quality.
Thank you. I'm a high quality PNG floating around.
Thank you. I'm a high-quality PNG floating around.
Oh, well I can't wait for your 3D!
Aww, well, I can't wait for your 3D!
Thank you Calli. It's going to be fun, very fun. See, I want to sing with you in 3D again.
Thank you, Calli. It's going to be fun, very fun. I want to sing with you in 3D again.
We'll do it.
Yeah, just like we did it the fast, yeah?
Just like we did it the first time, yeah?
Yeah, let's do it.
Definitely. All righty then. Well, since my body is fixed now, I think I should be heading off to do my Nephlim duties, maybe perhaps an idol meeting.
Definitely. All righty then. Well, since my body is fixed now, I think I should be heading off to do my nephilim duties, maybe perhaps an idol meeting.
Idol meeting!
Maybe perhaps an idol meeting that I've been that I've been getting an emergency alert for for a bit. Get out of our room! Not in my karaoke room, Iris!
An idol meeting that I've been getting an emergency alert for for a bit. Get out of our room! Not in my karaoke room, IRyS!
I need to go. I'm a fly. Get out, get out! Iris! Get out, Iris! You're a virus! Get out! She's she's leaving now. Yay.
I need to go. I'm a fly. Get out, get out! IRyS, you virus, get out! She's leaving now. Yay.
I was uh I was really quiet. I was lonely. I mean, I know that I have my dead beats here, but it's even better with friends, right? Yeah.
I was really quiet. I was lonely. I mean, I know that I have my Deadbeats here, but it's even better with friends, right? Yeah.
Anyway, I guess we should sing some more songs. Is that okay?
I think I've sufficiently rested enough.
Okay. Well, let's sing. Let's continue singing. That's what we're here for, right? I've got a couple more songs in me. So, let's go!
Utaimashou!
Let's sing!
「明日の午後は雨が降る」と ぽつり
"Tomorrow afternoon, it will rain," it quietly drops
耳鳴り 啓示 そんな何か 「気をつけて」
A ringing in my ears, a revelation, something like "Be careful"
過程の収穫にわか雨の 標的たちは
The convergence of processes, the targets of the sudden rain
誰も知らない これはつまり 未来予知
Nobody knows, this is in other words future prediction
「明日バスに乗るな」
"Don't take the bus tomorrow"
「事故が起きるから」
"Because an accident will happen"
最適な温度で 僕は生き行く
At the optimal temperature, I will live on
イカサマライフゲーム 奸智 がんくみ 揃えたジョーカーは 嘲 笑 う
Ikasama Life Game, the jokers with their necks aligned sneer
笑う
Laughing,
やがて
eventually,
感情は消え去った
emotions vanished.
いつか見た憧れ 翳れてく夢はマガイモノ
A longing I once saw, fading dreams are phonies.
嘲う
Sneering,
ひとり
alone,
祈れ 導きのままに
praying, as guided.
「明日のデートには行くな」と ぽつり
"Don't go on a date tomorrow," it quietly says.
陰をさす寒気 抑え込んで 札を引いた
Suppressing the chill casting a shadow, I drew a card.
過程の収束 にわか雨の 標的たちは
The process of convergence, the targets of the sudden rain
何も知らない 僕がそれを 選んだって
know nothing, even though I chose that,
誰かが言っていた
someone said,
「あの子は独りで」
"That girl is all alone,"
帰りのホームから 足を滑らせイクがさまらいふげ-
slipping from the platform on the way home—
イカサマライフゲーム 雁首揃えたジョーカーは 笑う
It's an ikasama life game, the jokers lined up sneer,
やがて 感情は消え去った
eventually, emotions vanished.
それでも存在理由など 後で決めるもの
Even so, reasons for existence and such are things to be decided later.
嘲う ひとり 祈れ 導きのままに
Sneering, alone, praying, as guided.
気づいた代償 答えに隠された
The price I realized, hidden in the answer,
さよなら愛しき日々 戻れないのは僕だけでいいから
goodbye beloved days, it's fine if only I cannot go back.
愛しき日々も戻れないのは 僕だけでいいから
beloved days, it's fine if only I cannot go back.
イカサマライフゲーム 雁首揃えたジョーカーは 笑う
It's an ikasama life game, the jokers lined up sneer,
やがて 未来予報は訪れる
eventually, foresight visits.
最後の通達 いやに明解で 憎らしい明日
The final notification, unpleasantly clear and spiteful,
「明日 君は」 「どう頑張ったって死にますよ」
"Tomorrow, you," "Will die no matter how hard you try."
イカサマライフゲーム 雁首揃えたジョーカーは 笑う
It's an ikasama life game, the jokers lined up sneer,
ワラエ ババ抜きじゃ仕方ないに
laugh, it can't be helped since it's Old Maid,
おかえり感情 死ぬほどの不安が愛しくて
Welcome back, emotions, my anxiety to the point of death is so dear,
笑う ひとり 祈れ 導きのままに
sneering, alone, praying, as guided.
明日 雨降るかな
I wonder if it will rain tomorrow.
裾が濡れたなら 乾くの待って 水面を叩いて跳ねた
If the hem got wet, waiting for it to dry, splashing on the water surface and jumping,
君が教えてくれたんだ
you taught me that.
僕は強くない 握っていてくれた
I am not strong, you were holding my hand,
この手を離さなきゃだめだ
I must let go of this hand.
ひとりでもゆくよ たとえ辛くても
I will go alone, even if it is painful,
みんなで見たい夢は 必ず持ってくよ
I will definitely carry the dream we all want to see together.
みんなとがいいな みんなとがよかった
Being with everyone is nice, being with everyone was great,
でも目覚めた朝 誰もいないんだね
but on the morning I woke up, no one is there.
もう振り返っても 誰の影もない
Even if I look back now, there is no one's shadow.
水たまりだけが光ってた
Only puddles were glowing.
生きるということ
What it means to live
それは立ち向かっていくこと
is to face head-on and keep going.
それがわかったなら
Once you realize that,
あとは踏み出す勇気だけ
all you need is the courage to take a step.
どこまでもゆくよ
I will go anywhere,
ここで知ったこと 幸せという夢 叶えてみせるよ
making the dream of happiness I learned here come true.
みんなと離れても どんなに遠くなっても
Even if I'm apart from everyone, no matter how far I go,
新しい朝に この子は生きるよ
I will live on in the new morning.
ひとりでもゆくよ
I will go even if I'm alone.
死にたくなっても 声が聞こえるよ 死んではいけないと
Even if I want to die, I can hear a voice telling me I mustn't.
たとえ辛くても 闇に閉ざされても
Even if it's painful, even if I'm locked in darkness,
心の奥には 明かりが灯ってるよ
a light is still burning deep inside my heart.
巡って流れて 時はうつろいの日々
Revolving and flowing, days where time shifts away—
もう何があったか 思い出せないけど
though I can no longer remember what happened,
目を閉じてみれば みんなの笑い声 なぜかそれが今 一番の宝物
when I close my eyes, everyone's laughter somehow feels like my greatest treasure now.
ありがとう
Thank you.
Now, let's sing one more song.
離れるほどさみしくなる 全てが愛おしい
The further apart we are, the lonelier it gets; everything is so dear.
セピアの心情を 開いてはまた思いふける SAKURA Days
Opening up my sepia emotions and reminiscing once more—SAKURA Days.
一陣の風に 揺れた髪が懐かしい 賑わいと温もりを運んでくれた
Hair swaying in a gust of wind feels nostalgic, carrying hustle, bustle, and warmth to me.
お陰で色づいた花 ある者は恋い焦がれて
Flowers dyed in color thanks to it; some yearn in love,
ある者は皆で歌い合い
while others sing together with everyone.
千望のマナザシを 抜けるものも
Some gaze forward, breaking through the longing gaze...
舞い散る夜風に 触れた切な香わしい
Touching the fleetingly fragrant night breeze as the petals flutter.
さよならとありがとうを共におくるよ お陰でまた好きになった
I'll send both "goodbye" and "thank you," learning to love again thanks to you.
去る者を追えるはずなく 来る者は拒めるわけない
There's no way I can chase those who leave, nor reject those who come.
故に尊い 桜色の日々よ
Therefore, these cherry blossom-colored days are so precious.
寂しさをたどる すべてが愛おし
Tracing the loneliness, everything is so dear,
セピアの心情を
keeping my sepia emotions
開いては また想いふける
open as I sink into thought once again.
桜 Days 遥か彼方響く 君の声に耳を澄ませば
SAKURA Days... If I strain my ear to hear your voice echoing from afar,
少なからず その温もり想い出せるように
so that I can still recall at least a bit of that warmth,
年とした寂ししさも 風情と成る 桜 Days
even the loneliness of aging becomes graceful—SAKURA Days.
桜 Days 桜 Days 少なからず その温もり想い出せるように
SAKURA Days, SAKURA Days... So that I can still recall at least a bit of that warmth,
巡り咲く 桜 Days 麗しき
blooming in turn, SAKURA Days... Oh, lovely...
桜 Days 桜 Days 桜 Days 桜 Days
SAKURA Days, SAKURA Days, SAKURA Days, SAKURA Days.
Thank you, everyone, thank you so much for coming to my karaoke party.
I have one more announcement, two more announcements, but one really big one.
I have one more announcement—two more announcements, but one really big one.
Everybody, it's my one year anniversary with Universal Music as a major artist. Yay!
Everybody, it's my one-year anniversary with Universal Music as a major artist. Yay!
Pachipachipachipachi, yay yay yay yay! Yay!
Clap, clap, clap, yay, yay, yay! Yay!
So everyone, I would like to introduce to you Cinderella LP! LP!
So everyone, I would like to introduce to you... SINDERELLA LP! LP!
That's right, everybody. We've got a vinyl release coming out.
And orders are going to open up tonight, so if you don't want to wait six months to get my merch...
or you can get both. Both is good, too. But if you don't want to wait, yay Mori Store!
you can go ahead and get this, or you can get both. Both is good, too. Yay, Mori Store!
Of course, I wasn't going to leave you guys without a vinyl. Nope, nope, nope.
I'm a big fan of records myself. So, yay, it's out now. Oh, looks like it's out!
Okay, it's out. You guys can get it. Check the link in the description if you want to grab it.
The vinyl's out. You can go purchase it. Yay! Yeah, so you guys can check it out. Yay!
I'm so happy. I'm so happy! I hope you guys get it. I can't wait to play it on my little, my little phonograph, my little turntable.
I'm so happy! I'm so happy! I hope you guys get it. I can't wait to play it on my little phonograph, my little turntable.
I'm very excited, so I hope you guys will get it as well. LP, LP.
Already bought? Oh my gosh, you guys are fast. Wow.
You guys are really fast. Ha ya! Eh, sugoi, katte kudasai ne, LP ne. So, meccha meccha kakkokii kore.
You guys are really fast, ha-ya! Please buy it, LP! It's super, super cool, this one.
So, ne, Re-chan, ano, suteki na art ne, arimasu ne, kono jacket.
And, you know, Re-chan, like, there's that lovely art, right, for this jacket.
Yeah, it's also super limited in quantity, they are now, they are now telling me. It's very limited, um, because we can't, we can't make a million of these. You guys know that there's, you know, kind of...
There's some, I don't know, you should get it now. You should get it now is what I'm trying to say.
Was what I'm trying to say! I'm so happy, I'm so excited. Um, so yeah, please grab it. Thank you so much, everyone!
And I have one last thing to announce. I have a cover coming out. Um, I don't know exactly when, cuz it's being checked.
It should be within the next day or two days or so. But...
Chotto samune, misete kudasai!
Hold on, show us a sneak peek!
What song is it? What song is it? What song is it? Salamander!
So please, uh, tanoshimi ni shite kudasai ne. Please look forward to it. I'm really, really proud of this one.
So please look forward to it. I'm really, really proud of this one.
It turned out super good, and I think you guys are going to love it. So, yeah, please look forward.
It turned out super good, and I think you guys are going to love it. So, yeah, please look forward to it!
And with that being said, you guys, uh, I'm your Mori. I hope that you'll remember me. This is a really fun stream.
And with that being said, you guys, um, I'm your Mori. I hope that you'll remember me. This is a really fun stream.
Thank you so much, you guys. Thanks for spending time with me, thanks for singing with me.
And I guess I'll catch you guys on the flip side, okay? Everybody take care, be sure to grab the merch again, that would make me happy.
And yeah, with that being said, everybody, I'll see you later. Thank you for coming! Bye-bye!
Gaikotsu-chan, come here. Bye-bye! See you everyone, mata ne! Peace out! Bye-bye!
Tired of owning useless items you'll never use
because you got lured in by that low, low price of 19.99?
Well, fear not, because on today's shopping program, Shop Till You Drop Dead,
featuring Calliope Mori.
None of our items are 19.99! Haha! Oh no!
Get ready to feast your eyes on some premium tier items
you'll literally want to gouge your eyes out if you don't own them out of sheer FOMO and additional existential dread of the emptiness of your life without them. You need these items.
You need that!
Why not get a sick poster of your one and only boy
to display at work and assert your dominance over your friends?
That's right, folks! Mori Calliope's special birthday poster features Mori Calliope rocking out at a concert she definitely did,
with an outfit she definitely wore!
You won't want to miss this premium item 'cause once it's gone, it's gone for good! Fuck you, scalpers, get it now!
Ever wanted to bathe yourself in sweet smelling, delicious purple liquid?
Well, I sure can't relate. But if you do,
then you better get your hands on this special duel set of bath bombs from Mori Calliope's favorite premium Underworld Onsen!
They come in two scents: Mori Rose and Death-sensei Purple Mist.
Get your sad, you smell like shit!
Thirsty? Surrounded by hot e-girls? Who the hell isn't? But too bad for you,
that's no e-girl on your mug, it's your dad! Your Mori Dad!
With an exclusive design by Mori Calliope father to all, you'll be feeling like number one as you sip your stress, anxiety, and existential dread away!
Don't miss your chance to grab it, dummy!
Lil' swag lord, boof, oof, yeah, lil' swag lord...
Plush comes with one outfit. Design details differ from final version. No trees are guaranteed to be saved by the making of this plush.
So what are you waiting for, deadbeat? If you get the whole set,
a limited number of deadbeats will get a hand-signed postcard! They're gonna sell out best 'cause I really like my hand,
but never fear, if you buy the full set, you'll get a duplicated autograph postcard! Remember, deadbeats, shop until your dead!
Beats! Get it, dead beats! Like the name of the fans! Haha! Haha!
Yo, shut the fuck up, no one's laughing at that shit.
Wait, Mori, no, I'm sorry, man. I'm laughing at it.
No wait, don't hit me! Please don't hit me! Stop! Stop that shit! No more! Oh, it hurts! Oh, I feel pain!
Minasan!
What's up!
Dead beats, lurking now, dead beats, lurking now
Dead beats, lurking now, dead beats, lock it down
Mina ni naru made
Until it becomes everyone's
Live Blu-ray Release!
Here, when it came out, that's what's up
Mawase bakka mawase, sore yase no se, let me shake it up
Spin it round and round, let's go, let me shake it up
Tired of owning useless items you'll never use
because you got lured in by that low, low price of 19.99?
Well, fear not, because on today's shopping program, Shop Till You Drop Dead, featuring...
Mori! None of our items are $19.99!
Oh no!
Get ready to feast your eyes on some premium tier items
you'll literally want to gouge your eyes out if you don't own them out of sheer FOMO
and additional existential dread of the emptiness of your life without them.
You need these items!
YOU NEED THEM!
Why not get a sick poster of your one and only boy to display at work
and assert your dominance over your friends?
That's right, folks! Mori Calliope's
special birthday poster features Mori Calliope rocking out at a concert
she definitely did with an outfit she definitely wore!
You won't want to miss this premium item 'cause once it's gone, it's gone for good.
Get it now!
Ever wanted to bathe yourself in sweet smelling,
delicious purple liquid?
Well, I sure can't relate! But if you do,
then you better get your hands on this special dual set of bath bombs
from Mori Calliope's favorite premium Underworld Onsen!
They come in two scents: Mori Rose and Death Sensei Purple Mist.
Get yours today, you smell like shit.
Thirsty? Surrounded by hot e-girls? Who the hell isn't?
But too bad for you, that's no e-girl on your mug, it's your dad!
Your Mori Dad! With an exclusive design by Mori Calliope,
father to all, you'll be feeling like number one as you sip your stress,
anxiety, and existential dread away! Don't miss your chance to grab it, dummy!
Lil' swag lord...
Do you want a half-stitch deadbeat? Do you want a safe tree deadbeat?
Lil' swag lord... got to get your swag...
So what are you waiting for, deadbeat?
If you get the whole set, a limited number of deadbeats will get a hand-signed postcard!
They're gonna sell out fast 'cause I really like my hand, but never fear,
if you buy the full set, you get a duplicated autograph postcard!
Remember, deadbeats, shop until you're dead! Beats!
Get it? Deadbeats!
Look, the name of the fans!
Yo, shut the fuck up, no one's laughing at that shit!
Wait, Mori, no, I'm sorry, Mori!
No, no, don't hit me, please, don't hit me!
Stop! Stop that shit!
No more! Mori, please! Ah, god!
Oh, it hurts! Oh, I feel pain!
皆さん、What's up?
Everyone, what's up?
mera mera burning all day
真夏の楽園
Midsummer paradise
mera mera 焦がれて
Mera mera, scorched
灰になる まで
until you turn to ashes
メロメロに させて
Make me fall head over heels
さあ踊り狂いっちゃって
Come on, dance like crazy
火炙り パラダイス
Incineration paradise
go up and down
silly bakka, silly ba
Silly idiot, silly id-
シリアスな shit, lemme shake it up
Serious shit, lemme shake it up